Luciano Nicolás Díaz

Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina



luchodiaz1995@gmail.com



01159102957



linkedin.com/in/lucianonicolasdiaz

Summary

I am a software developer with experience in building websites and web applications. I am specializing in the frontend area using Angular as framework, but I also have professional experience working with .NET, as I was included in the development of REST APIs, web pages with ASP NET using .NET Framework 4.5. I have also worked with databases using MS SQL Server, T-SQL and authentication with Firebase.

Experience

Full Stack Engineer

Banco Supervielle

Aug 2022 - Present (7 months)

Following the Scrum methodology, using Trello

Maintenance and Development of a backoffice system about insurance and assistance

Works on the frontend using Angular and Fuse template

Works with software providers

Full Stack Engineer

IUDÚ

Mar 2022 - Oct 2022 (8 months)

Following the Scrum methodology, using Jira.

Maintenance and Development of the On Boarding section from the app hosted on the Play/App Store ($IUD\acute{U}$).

Maintenance and Development of an internal system from the company to allow the users to check the status of the new on boardings from the clients.

Work in Squads.

Use especially MS Sql Server, .Net Core 3.1, Angular, and Git (with respositories alocated on Azure Dev Ops).

Full Stack Engineer

Globant

May 2021 - Mar 2022 (11 months)

Follow the Scrum methodology, using Jira and speaking on english.

Maintenance and Development a platform for the sale of advertising space.

Unit Testing (Karma, Jasmine, NUnit).

Use especially .Net Core 3.1, C#, JQuery, JavaScript, Git.

Full Stack Engineer

Time Solution Software

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Development and maintenance of Web Applications (Web Forms, Web Api, .NET Framework).

Development and maintenance of Web Desktops (Windows Forms). Managment and development of Data Bases (MS SQL Server, T-SQL). Communication team through Discord and Trello. Work using Git and push to a GitHub respository.

Education

***∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

University Technician in Computer Systems, Tecnología informática/Tecnología de sistemas informáticos

Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

***∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

University Technician in Programming, Programación informática Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

Skills

Firebase • TypeScript • scss • .NET Core • Angular • Microsoft SQL Server • REST APIs • Programación orientada a objetos (OOP) • ASP.NET • C#